Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran School of Art + Design records, circa 1908-2012 COR0009.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative records, 1960-2013; Series 12
  - General administrative file, 1962-2012; Series 12 subseries 7
    - GW Billing, 1969 Fall; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - GW Billing, 1970 Spring; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence GW, 1968-1969; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - GW Curriculum, 1969 Spring; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Curriculum GW, 1969; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Curriculum GW, 1969-1970; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - GW Correspondence, 1969-1970; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - GW - Class time slots, 1970; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Class Schedule - GW (with Fall quota list), 1970; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - GW, 1970 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - George Washington University: Tuition, pre 1962; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - George Washington University: Tuition, 1962-1967; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - George Washington University: Grade Sheets, 1966-1967; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - George Washington University: Catalogs and Bulletins, 1967-1968; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - George Wasington University: Tuition:, 1967; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - George Wasington University: Grade Sheets, 1967 Fall; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - GW Billing, 1968 Spring; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Bulletins GW - Commencement, 1967-1968; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Class Lists GW, 1968 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - GW Billing, 1968 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - GW Summer Term: Correspondence, 1968 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Veterans, 1970 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folders 37-38)
    - Veterans, 1969-1970; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Foreign Student, 1969-1970; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Voc. Rehab. - MD & VA, 1970 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Veterans Admin. Voc. Rehab, 1970 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - MD, VA, DC Vocational Rehab, 1969-1970; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Veterans Admin. Vocational Rehab, 1969-1970; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Local Galleries, Art Centers, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Addresses - Women's Committee, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Docent Mailing List, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - D.C. Consortium - Addresses, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Addresses - DC Commission on Arts and Humanities, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Addresses- Friends of Corocran Docents Council, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Addresses - NASAD, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Addresses - Jackson Governance, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Addresses - Press, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Addresses - Area Schools, circa 1985-1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Art School Committee Meeting Monday, 1990 April 30; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1990 February 5; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1989 November 13; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1989 September 18; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Subcommittees Goals for Academic Year, 1988-1989; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Art School Committee Meeting Agenda/Minutes, 1988; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1990 December 17; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 November 19; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1990 October 22; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 September 24; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 July 16; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 June 25; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 47)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 April 23; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 48)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 March 26; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 49)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 January 29; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 50)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1990 May 21; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 51)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1990 February 26; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 52)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1990 January 16; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 53)
    - Development, circa 1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 44, Folder 54)
    - Facilities: FSORT, 1985-1989; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 52)
    - Facilities: FDEPT, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 53)
    - Facilities: Spreiregen, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 54)
    - Facilities: Studley, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 55)
    - Facilities: Oliver Carr Co., circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 56)
    - Facilities: Lansburgh Development, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 57)
    - Facilities: Bennett Bldg., circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 58)
    - Facilities: Lansburgh, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 59)
    - Facilities: 15th & M Zoning Commission Order, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 60)
    - Facilities: St. Mary's Academy, Alexandria, Virginia, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 61)
    - Facilities: Joseph Alfandre & Co., Inc. Kentlands Gaithersburg, MD, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 62)
    - Facilities: McGraw-Hill Building 3939 Wisconsin Avenue, N.W. Brannock Associates, INC., circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 63)
    - Facilities: 919 E Street, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 64)
    - Facilities: Bldg Museum, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 65)
    - National Endownment for the Arts (NEA), 1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 66)
    - Julius Lansburgh Furniture Store 901 F Street NW, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 67)
    - Studley/TDRS, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 68)
    - Downtown Develop. District TDR's/Office of Plan/ Green, Gross, Fondersmith, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 69)
    - Rehab-Masonic BLDG New Construction 9th + F/ Architects, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 70)
    - Tower/Antonect, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 71)
    - Ad Hoc Space Committee Demnon, Wyatt, Rosenbaum, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 72)
    - B+G Trustees, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 73)
    - Correspondece B-D, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 74)
    - Correspondece E-J, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 75)
    - Correspondence K-N, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence O-T, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 77)
    - Eric Rudd Beaver Mill School of Contemporary Art, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 78)
    - Springtide The Shipley School, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 79)
    - Gary M. Turnquist, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 80)
    - Correrspondence Dean's Office Bruce Yenawine Dick Slade, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 81)
    - Winter, Dr. Rob, circa 1980s-1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 57, Folder 82)
    - Petition to Grant Credits and Deliver BFA Diploma, 33725; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Marketing Plan for the Sale of 1340 21st Street, NW, on Behalf of the Corcoran Museum of Art, Charles E. Smith Companies, circa 1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Beat the Heat! Handheld-fan, circa 1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - EILC, 1981-1984; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - The Mayor's Art Award, 1985; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Annual School Benefit: Litchenstein, Carp, Cowart, Diamonstein - Cassette Tape, 34464; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Sale of 1340 21st Street & 2102 O Street NW, Washington DC, circa 1990; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Jewels of the Romanovs: Treasurers of the Russian Imperial Court, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - The Moscow Studio A Five Year Printmaking Retrospective 1991-1996, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: a Project of the Batuz Foundation, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Justin Lemeges Print, 1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - MD Accreditation- CE, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Larrabee Scholarship, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - VACOP Strategic Planning Meetings 1998, Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - VACOP Q's completed, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - CANVAS- Environmental scan results, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Questionaires, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - VACOP Information Sheets, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - VACOP, 2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Young Audiences in DC, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - CAVE Center for Collaborative Art and Visual Education, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - YMCA Partnerships, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - ACEnet F.I.P.S.E Grant, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - White Flint Mall Corcoran Mural Project, 1994 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - School Benefits Beaux Arts Masquerade, 1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Berlin, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - White Flint Mall, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Stephen McClymont, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - AP Mtg To Type, 1998 May 15; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Wingspread File, 1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Visual Arts Community Outreach Program/ VACOP Strategic Plan, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Jewish Community Center of Northern Viriginia, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - AICAD Dean's Meeting, 1998 March 5-7; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Payroll Spring, 1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - CE Classes for Seniors space agreement, 1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Rockville Arts Place, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Chairs' Council Minutes & Agendas, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Constance Larrabee Correspondence, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Vancouver AICAD, 1998 April 3-7; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - CE/OP Catalog, 1998 Fall; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Friends of Fillmore Arts Center, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Asian Americans LEAD, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Judy Byron CAMP Coordinator, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Library Committee, 1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - DCPS Arts & Humanities Initative, 1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Arts in a Living Downtown, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - AICAD Annual Data Summary, 1997-1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - AICAD Annual Data Summary, 1996-1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - HEADS Report, 1997-1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - HEADS Worksheets, 1997-1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - IPEDS, 1993; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - CBOO, 1994-1995; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - CBOO, 1995-1996; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - CBOO, 1996-1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Museum School Heads Meeting, 1993 February 18; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - NASAD Evaluation, 1997 November 3-7; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - VACOP Coordinators, 1997 Fall; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - NASAD & AICAD Meeting, 1997 Fall; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - MSA Annual Institution Profile, 1996-1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Marshall Heights Community Dev. Org, 1996-1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Lisa Strong Academic Studies, 1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Chairs' Council Min & Agendas, 1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Constance Larrabee Correspondence, 1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Position Announcement Samples, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Teaching Art & Design in the 21st Century, 1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Library Kraft/MCI Workshops, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Notice of Final Rule Making, 1993; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Berlin School Exchange, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - NASAD 1996 Annual Meeting, Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Sample of Berkman, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - DCAG Searches, 1996; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Quadrangle Dev., 1996; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Candidacy for Accreditation, 1997; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - DACUM Resource Center, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Lepczyk v. CSA, circa 1990s; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Development Fund, 1991-1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - HEADS Annual Report, 1998; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - HEADS Data Summaries, 1991-2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Catalog Pages, 2000 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Scholarships, 2000 Fall; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - VACOP Scholarships, 2000 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - VACOP Scholarships, 2000 Spring; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - VACOP Scholarships, 1999 Fall; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Complimentary Classses Donated/Awarded, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - VACOP, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Hong Hoa Ly Thi, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - VACOP, 1999 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - VACOP, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Budget Meetings with MW, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Focus Budget, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Budget Meetings, 2000 Spring; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Budget Report from Sarah, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Mail Service, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - AFA App. Fees, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Departments, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Honoraria, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Advertising, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Phone Bills, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Postage, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Printing, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Focus, 2001 March; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - AU, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Faculty Contracts, 2000 Spring; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Contracts, 1999 Summer; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Focus Fax Material, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Corcoran - Photojournalism Poster, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Focus, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Scholarship Form, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - CE & YP Budgets, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Children's & Young People's Program PO's, 1999; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - Professional Training, circa 2000; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 84, Folder 33)
    - Faculty Orientation, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Record Reports, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - FRP, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Fillmore Move, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Foundation for Educational Innovation/Partner, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Jeanne Griffin, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Hayes Friedman Classical Drawing, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - HAMP Print Workshop, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - HI/SCIP, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Hermitage, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Images, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Independent Contractors, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Budget Projections, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Interior Design Certificate, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Kirk-Whitney, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Lab Techs, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - LFCC, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Library Lab Policy, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - LIbrary Info, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - The London Institute, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - CBoO-Stuff, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - CE Customer Service, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - CCAD Closing Policy, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - CCAD vs. other schools AICAD Reports, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - CHE/MSA, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - CPHE/SAO/ACAP, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 26)
    - CE Chairs Meeting, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 27)
    - CE Deans & Director Conference, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 28)
    - CEUS, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 29)
    - Corcoran Awaards, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 30)
    - CLHE, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 31)
    - Course Code Revision, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 32)
    - Course Benefit Acknowledgement, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 33)
    - Bill Christenberry Proposal, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 34)
    - Curriculum, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 35)
    - Curriculum Retreat, 1999; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 36)
    - Dod: DiSanto, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 37)
    - DC College Access Act, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 38)
    - Drawing & Painting Policies, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 39)
    - Donated Classes, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 40)
    - Claudette DuCran, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 41)
    - Education Dept., 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 42)
    - Avera Melissa, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 43)
    - Chair Evaluations, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 44)
    - Credit/hr vs. Contact hr., 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 45)
    - Catalogue, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 46)
    - Ceramics Lab Assistants, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 47)
    - Self Study, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 48)
    - Camp, 1999; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 49)
    - Givens, Sharon, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 50)
    - Burleith, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 51)
    - Blackrock Center in Germantown, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 52)
    - Marketing report Al Landa, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 53)
    - Robyn McLlender, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 54)
    - Meeting w/ Sammy, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 55)
    - MSA, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 56)
    - Millennium Arts Center, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 57)
    - NAEA, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 58)
    - NAS Group decision maling & learning, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 59)
    - Open House, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 60)
    - Open Program Brochure, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 61)
    - Anette Polan, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 62)
    - Trik Pollet, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 63)
    - Profolio Dev Prep Class, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 64)
    - Potential Software for Scheduling, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 65)
    - Pre-College, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 66)
    - Pricing Study, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 67)
    - Profit Sharing, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 68)
    - Promotions, 2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 69)
    - Proof Read Cat., 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 70)
    - Reaccreditation, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 71)
    - Reston Comm. Center, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 72)
    - Sabbaticals, 2001-2002; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 73)
    - Scholarships, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 74)
    - School of Specific Learning, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 75)
    - Self Study, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 76)
    - Saort Range Facilities Requests, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 77)
    - Silent Auction, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 78)
    - Skope los Studio, 1998-2001; Series 12 subseries 7 (Box 87, Folder 79)